# John Warren

#### **Software Developer**

- 07746891363 johnv8@hotmail.co.uk
- johnw-north.github.io/react-portfolio/ github.com/johnw-north

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS/SASS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript

- React Framework
- Node JS
- Git Version Control

- Rest API
- Linux
- Testing
- SQL

## **PROJECTS**

#### Petrol Pal (Web App)

The goal was providing a clean experience for working out the cost of car fuel, between two user selected locations. Made with React and utilising Google Maps API for location requests. Additionally, an implemented card system was later developed to allow multiple journey calculations in one page.

#### **Cyber Quest (Appointment Website)**

Commercial website, designed to be easy to use for all ages and implement an appointment API. UX was a high priority needed multiple iterations of testing.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Cyber Quest Virtual Reality - Software Developer (2020 - 2022)

- Front end development
- UE4 Scripting
- Android deployment

#### **Smart Plumbing –** eCommerce Manager (2021 – 2022)

- Manage customer accounts, queries and invoices
- Querying and rectifying and discrepancies with delivery partners
- Maintain and update e-commerce store
- Discuss product SEO implementation with team

### **The Original Factory Shop –** Merchandiser Admin (2019-2020)

- Find trends in sales to predict stock levels
- Report forecasts for marketing
- Weekly Commercial meeting with range wide discussion

### **Asda** – Assistant Department Manager (2015-2019)

- The training of newer colleagues
- Presenting store data every morning with all departments
- Planning team schedules and tasks

# **EDUCATION**

- CS50 Harvard Introduction to Computer Science
- Manchester Metropolitan University Accounting and Finance (Certificate of Higher Education)
- Ashton Sixth Form BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma in Business (Management) D, D, M
- All Saints GCSEs in English, Mathematics and Science